Guide to the ACT UP New York records, 1969, 1982-1997 [bulk 1987-1995]
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series X. Published and near-print materials, 1969, 1982-1995, n.d; 557278; 58 boxes
  - X.D. Newsletters and serials, 1982-1995, n.d.; 557529; 14 boxes
    - AIDS Forum, New York, 1989; 557563 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 7)
    - AIDS in Prison Project, New York, 1993; 557564 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Patient Care, New York, 1987, 1992; 557565; Not microfilmed (Box 180, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Policy and Law, Washington, DC, 1987; 557566 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 10)
    - AIDS-Related Community Services (ARCS) News, New York, 1989; 557567 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 11)
    - AIDS Targeted Information Newsletter (ATIN), Washington, DC, 1989; 557568 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 12)
    - AIDS Treatment Data Network, Washington, DC, 1992; 557569 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 13)
    - AIDS Treatment News, San Francisco, California, 1986-1995; 557570 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 14-17)
    - AIDS Watch, England, 1989; 557571 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 18)
    - AIDS/HIV Record, Washington, DC, 1989; 557572 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 8)
    - American Association of Women Voters, New York, 1985; 557573 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 23)
    - American Indian Community House (AICH), New York, 1991, 1994; 557574 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 22)
    - American Medical Association news releases, Chicago, Illinois, 1982-1985; 557575 (Reel 147, Box 180, Folder 24)
    - The Atlantic, New York, 1987; 557576; Not microfilmed (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - ATOBA, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1986; 557577 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 2)
    - B & G 1.4-5, New York, 1990 May-Jun; 557578; Not microfilmed (Box 181, Folder 3)
    - Being Alive, Los Angeles, California, 1992; 557579 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Body Positive, New York, 1989-1990, 1992-1995; 557580; Folder 7, covering 1992, and folder 9, covering part of 1994, were not microfilmed. (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 6-10)
    - El Boletin, Connecticut, 1994; 557581 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 14)
    - Bronx AIDS News, New York, 1992; 557582 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 11)
    - The Bulletin, New York State Insurance Department, 1993; 557583 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 12)
    - Bulletin for Experimental Treatments for AIDS (BETA), San Francisco, California, 1994-1995; 557584 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Canadian Journal of Infectious Diseases, Québec, 1992; 557585; Not microfilmed (Box 181, Folder 15)
    - The Cancer Chronicles, New York, 1990; 557586 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 13)
    - Cancer Research, Maryland, 1987; 557587; Not microfilmed (Box 181, Folder 14)
    - Catalyst, Washington, DC, 1987; 557588 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 16)
    - CATO Institute, 1986; 557589 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 17)
    - CD Summary 42.11, Oregon, 1993 Jun 1; 557590 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Centers for Disease Control, Atlanta, Georgia, 557591 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 18)
      - AIDS Weekly, 1987; 557592 (Reel 148, Box 181, Folder 18)
      - AIDS/HIV Surveillance, 1989; 557593 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Chemical and Engineering News, Washington, DC, 1987-1988; 557594; Not microfilmed (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - City Health Information (CHI), Department of Health, New York City, 1993; 557595 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 3)
    - City Limits, New York, 1995; 557596 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 4)
    - Clinical Congress News, United Kingdom, 1991; 557597 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 5)
    - Community Research Initiative (CRI) NY, New York, 1991; 557598 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 6)
    - Conexiones en Accion, San Francisco, California, 1994; 557599 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 7)
    - Cornell Clinical Trials, New York, 1991; 557600 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 8)
    - Critical Path AIDS Project, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1992-1995; 557601; Not microfilmed (Box 182, Folder 9-11)
    - El Cuerpo Positivo, New York, 1993; 557602 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 15)
    - Directorio de Recursos, New York, 1995; 557603 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 13)
    - Documentation of AIDS Issues and Research Foundation (DAIR) Update, San Francisco, California, 1985-1986; 557604 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 12)
    - Equal Time, Minnesota, 1989; 557605 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 17)
    - Extra, Washington, DC, 1989; 557606 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 18)
    - Family Research, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1987; 557607 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 19)
    - FDC Reports, Maryland, 557608
      - Blue Sheets, 1989; 557609 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 20)
      - Pink Sheets, 1989; 557610 (Reel 148, Box 183, Folder 1)
      - Pink Sheets, 1989; 557611 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), 557612
      - Bulletin, New York, 1988-1990; 557613 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 3)
      - Newsletter, New York, 1989-1990; 557614 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Gay and Lesbian Nation, San Diego, California, 1990; 557615; Not microfilmed (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Gay Men's Health Crisis (GMHC) Treatment News, New York, 1987-1992; 557616 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Global AIDS News: The Newsletter of the World Health Organization Global Programme on AIDS, Geneva, Switzerland, 1992; 557617 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Harvard, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1983; 557618 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 8)
    - HIV Hotline, New Mexico, 1992-1994; 557619 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 10)
    - HIV SERO Survey Unit, New York City, 1990; 557620 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 11)
    - HIV Treatment News, Wisconsin, n.d.; 557621 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 12)
    - HIV/AIDS, Atlanta, Georgia, 1993; 557622 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Health Access Foundation, California, 1990; 557623 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 13)
    - Health Education AIDS Liaison (HEAL), New York City, 1989-1993; 557624 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 14)
    - Health Education Resource Organization (HERO), Maryland, 1991; 557625 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 15)
    - HealthFacts, New York, 1990 Mar; 557626 (Reel 149, Box 183, Folder 16)
    - HX (Homo Xtra), New York City, 557627
      - 1992 Mar-Jun, 557628; Not microfilmed (Box 183, Folder 17-18)
      - 1992 Jul-Nov, 1993 Jan, 1994 Sep, 557629; Not microfilmed (Box 184, Folder 1-6)
    - Hope for the Future, Yonkers, New York, 1993; 557630 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 7)
    - The Housing Authority Journal, New York, 1991; 557631 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Humanist, New York, 1988; 557632; Not microfilmed (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - Image [section], San Francisco Examiner, San Francisco, California, 1989; 557633; Not microfilmed (Box 184, Folder 10)
    - Imperially Yours, New York, 1994-1995; 557634 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 11)
    - Infection Reporter, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1985; 557635 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Innovation, Kinderhook, New York, 1990; 557636 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 13)
    - Island Lifestyles, Hawaii, 1992; 557637; Not microfilmed (Box 184, Folder 14)
    - Journal of Health Care for the Poor and Underserved 5, no. 3, Nashville, Tennessee, 1994; 557638; Not microfilmed (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Journal of Immunotherapy, New York, 1992; 557639; Not microfilmed (Box 184, Folder 16)
    - Journal of Palliative Care, Montréal, Québec, 1988; 557640; Not microfilmed (Box 184, Folder 17)
    - Journal of the Physicians Association for AIDS Care, Chicago, Illinois, 1994; 557641; Not microfilmed (Box 184, Folder 18)
    - La Guia, New York, 1992; 557642 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 19)
    - Lambda Update, New York, 1990; 557643 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 20)
    - LAP Notes (Lesbian AIDS Project at the Gay Men's Health Crisis [GMHC]), New York, 1993; 557644 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 21)
    - Lavender Network, Oregon, 1992; 557645 (Reel 150, Box 184, Folder 22)
    - Lies of Our Times, New York, 1990; 557646; Premier issue; not microfilmed (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Medical Alert, 1993-1994; 557647 (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Medical Meetings, 1989; 557648; Not microfilmed (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Momentum, Washington, DC, 1989; 557649 (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Morbidity and Morality Weekly Report, Centers for Disease Control, Atlanta, Georgia, 1982-1989; 557650; Not microfilmed (Box 186)
    - Mother Jones, San Francisco, California, 1989; 557651; Not microfilmed (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - National AIDS Network, Washington, DC, 1988; 557652 (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 7)
    - National Coalition of Gay STD Services, Wisconsin, 1984; 557653 (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 8)
    - National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases (NIAID), Bethesda, Maryland, 1989-1994; 557654; Miscellaneous publications (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 9)
    - National Minority AIDS Council, Washington, DC, 1992; 557655 (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 10)
    - National Task Force on AIDS Prevention (NTFAP) Notes, San Francisco, California, 1994; 557656 (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 11)
    - Network News, Washington, DC, 1989; 557657 (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 12)
    - The News, Atlanta, Georgia, 1992-1993; 557658; Not microfilmed (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - Newsline, People with AIDS Coalition/NY (PWAC), New York, 1987, 1989-1995; 557659 (Reel 150, Box 185, Folder 14-20)
    - Newsweek, New York, 1985-1986; 557660; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Next magazine, New York, 1994; 557661; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Northwestern News, Illinois, 1984; 557662; Press releases (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Notes from the Underground, New York City, 1991-1994; 557663 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 4)
    - El Noticiero, Washington, DC, 1993; 557664 (Reel 148, Box 182, Folder 16)
    - Osborne Association Newsletter, New York City, 1991; 557665 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Outfront, Mayor's office, New York City, 1989; 557666 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 6)
    - The Outreach, Birmingham, Alabama, 1991; 557667 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 7)
    - PAAC NOTES (Physicians Association for AIDS Care), Chicago, Illinois, 1992; 557668; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Padma News, Seattle, Washington, 1985; 557669 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Passport, 1987 Jun-Jul; 557670; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Pediatric AIDS and HIV Infection, New York, 1992; 557671; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - People magazine, New York, 1985; 557672; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 12)
    - People with AIDS Coalition of Tucson (PACT), Tucson, Arizona, 1991; 557673 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 13)
    - PWA (People with AIDS) Support, New York, 1993-1994; 557674 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 14)
    - Pet Owner with AIDS/ARC (POWARS), New York, 1994; 557675 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 15)
    - PI Perspective, San Francisco, California, 1987-1994; 557676 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 24)
    - Piss and Vinegar, Washington, DC, 1989-1991; 557677 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 16)
    - Plain Truth, California, 1985; 557678; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 17)
    - Plus Voice, Chicago, Illinois, 1994; 557679; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 18)
    - Population Reports, Baltimore, Maryland, 1986; 557680 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 19)
    - Positively Aware, Chicago, Illinois, 1992-1995; 557681; Not microfilmed (Box 187, Folder 20-23)
    - Provincetown Positive, Provincetown, Massachusetts, 1994; 557682 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 25)
    - Public Health Service (PHS) Fact Sheet, US Department of Health and Human Services, 557683 (Reel 151, Box 187, Folder 26)
    - Queer Planet Review, Chicago, Illinois, n.d.; 557684; Advertisement (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Resist, Massachusetts, 1988; 557685 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Rethinking AIDS, San Francisco, California, 1992; 557686 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Rites magazine, Toronto, Ontario, 1988-1989; 557687; Not microfilmed (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Rush-Presbyterian-St. Luke's Medical Center, New York, 1990; 557688 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 5)
    - Science and Health, Brooklyn, New York, 1989; 557689; Not microfilmed (Box 188, Folder 6)
    - Scottish AIDS Newsletter, Scotland, 1991; 557690 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 8)
    - SIDA Ahora, People with AIDS Coalition/New York City, 1991-1992, 1994; 557691; Not microfilmed (Box 188, Folder 9-10)
    - SIECUS Report, Sex Information and Education Council of the U.S. 20.2, 1991 Dec/1992 Jan; 557692 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Engineering, California, 1989; 557693; Not microfilmed (Box 188, Folder 11)
    - Stats, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1990; 557694 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 12)
    - Stop the Violence, New York, 1992, 1995; 557695 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 13)
    - Tagline, New York, 1992; 557696 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 16)
    - Team Work, Fresno, California, 1991; 557697 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 17)
    - Time, New York, 1986, 1995; 557698; Not microfilmed (Box 188, Folder 18-19)
    - Treatment Action Group (TAG), New York, New York, 1994-1995; 557699; Not microfilmed (Box 188, Folder 14-15)
    - Treatment Review, New York, 1993; 557700 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 20)
    - Treatment Update 61, Canada, circa 1989; 557701 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 21)
    - University of California News, San Francisco, California, 1982; 557702 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 22)
    - Update, AIDS Services of Austin, Austin, Texas, 1991; 557703 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 23)
    - Update, National Minority AIDS Council, Washington, DC, 1995; 557704 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 24)
    - Vancouver People with AIDS, Vancouver, 1991; 557705 (Reel 151, Box 188, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Medical, Virginia, 1989; 557706; Not microfilmed (Box 188, Folder 26)
    - WBAI Folio, New York, 1990; 557707; Not microfilmed (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Whole Foods Project, New York, 1995; 557708 (Reel 151, Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Women Being Alive, Los Angeles, California, 1993 Summer; 557709 (Reel 151, Box 189, Folder 3)
    - World Health Organization (WHO) Press, Geneva, Switzerland, 1989; 557710 (Reel 151, Box 189, Folder 4)
    - WorldAIDS, London, England, 557711
      - 1 and 2, 1989 Jan and May; 557712 (Reel 151, Box 189, Folder 6)
      - Datafile, 1993 May; 557713 (Reel 151, Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 557714; None of these newspapers were microfilmed.
      - AIDS Action Now!, 1989 May; 557715; Pullout supplement (Box 190, Folder 1)
      - AIDS Info 42, 1989; 557716; This newspaper is in Dutch. (Box 190, Folder 2)
      - Baltimore Alternative 7, no. 10, 1992 Oct; 557717 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - Big Easy Times 1, no. 1, 1988 Aug 12; 557718 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - The Center Fold, 1990 Aug, 1992 Oct; 557719; This newspaper is based in Florida. (Box 190, Folder 5-6)
      - DCQ: The Fag Boys News, 557720
        - 1994 Jul 20-Aug 20, 557721 (Box 190, Folder 8)
        - No. 5, 1994 Sep 2-20; 557722 (Box 190, Folder 7)
      - Dimensions, 1989 Jun 4; 557723; This publication is from the Fifth International Conference on AIDS. (Box 190, Folder 9)
      - EDGE Magazine 233, 1992 Jun 17; 557724; This magazine is based in Los Angeles, California. (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - En Blanco y Negro 1, no. 1, 1990 Nov 1; 557725; This is a Spanish language ACT UP publication. (Box 190, Folder 11)
      - Frontera Gay 1, no. 12, 1993 May; 557726; This publication is in Spanish. (Box 190, Folder 12)
      - Gay Community News, 557727
        - 15, no. 31, 1988 Feb 21-27; 557728 (Box 190, Folder 13)
        - 16, no. 39, 1989 Apr 16-22; 557729 (Box 190, Folder 14)
      - De GAY Krant, 557730
        - No. 127, 1989 Mar 25; 557731 (Box 190, Folder 15-16)
        - No. 212, 1992 Oct 3; 557732 (Box 190, Folder 17)
      - Gaze 92, 1989 Jul 27; 557733; This newspaper is based in the Twin Cities, Minnesota. (Box 190, Folder 19)
      - GLC Voice, tenth year, issue #218, 1989 Aug 7; 557734 (Box 190, Folder 18)
      - The Guardian, 557735
        - 1988 Oct 12 and the Gay Community News 16, no. 13, 1988 Oct 9-15; 557736 (Box 190, Folder 20)
        - 42, no. 31 and 43, no. 15, 1990 May 30, 1991 Feb 6; 557737 (Box 190, Folder 21)
      - The Harvard Crimson, 1990 Jan 19; 557738 (Box 190, Folder 22, Folder 2)
      - IN Newsweekly 3, no. 38, 1994 May 22; 557739 (Box 190, Folder 23)
      - Just Out, 557740; This newspaper is based in Portland, Oregon.
        - Vol. 7, no. 9-10, 1990 Jul-Aug; 557741 (Box 191, Folder 1)
        - Vol. 9, no. 12, 1992 Oct; 557742 (Box 191, Folder 2)
        - Vol. 10, no. 19-20, 1993 Aug 15-Sep 1; 557743 (Box 191, Folder 3)
      - Movement Research, Performance Journal #6, 1993 Spring/Summer; 557744 (Box 191, Folder 4)
      - The New Common Good, 1990 Aug; 557745 (Box 191, Folder 5)
      - New York Native, no. 305, 1989 Feb 20; 557746 (Box 191, Folder 6)
      - The New York Times Magazine, 1988 Jan 31; 557747 (Box 191, Folder 7)
      - The News 5, no. 7, 1989 Apr 12; 557748; This newspaper is based in Atlanta, Georgia. (Box 191, Folder 8)
      - Nolo News 8, no. 4, 1988 Winter; 557749; This newspaper is based in Berkeley, California. (Box 191, Folder 9)
      - Outlines, 557750; This newspaper is based in Chicago, Illinois.
        - Vol. 5, no. 8, 1992 Jan; 557751 (Box 191, Folder 10)
        - Vol. 6, no. 5, 1992 Oct; 557752 (Box 191, Folder 11)
      - QC Quad 5, no. 7, 1988 Oct 10; 557753 (Box 191, Folder 12)
      - San Francisco Sentinel 18, no. 2, 1990 Jan 11; 557754 (Box 191, Folder 13)
      - The Wanderer 121, no. 11, 1988 Mar 17; 557755; This newspaper is based in St. Paul, Minnesota. (Box 191, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous clippings, 557756
        - ACT UP Boston. Attitude! 7, 1990 Sep; 557757 (Box 191, Folder 15)
        - Capital Action. We Demand a Cure, 1991 Oct 1; 557758; This newsprint handout was for a demonstration in Washington, DC. (Box 191, Folder 16)
        - Chicago Tribune, Section 5: 1-16, 1989 Nov 19; 557759 (Box 191, Folder 15)
        - Human Rights Watch Film Festival, 1992 May 8-17; 557760 (Box 191, Folder 16)
        - The March on Washington, 1993 Apr 25; 557761 (Box 191, Folder 16)
        - New York Newsday, Part III: Discovery: 1-16, 1989 Jun 13; 557762 (Box 191, Folder 15)
        - San Francisco Examiner, B: 1-8, 1989 Jun 4; 557763 (Box 191, Folder 15)
        - Welcome to New York, Stonewall 25, 1994 Jun; 557764; ACT UP New York distributed this mock "official" flier at the Stonewall 25 celebrations. (Box 191, Folder 15)
- Series XI. Ephemera, fliers, and handbills, 1988-1993, n.d.; 557765; 10 boxes
  Series XI. Ephemera, fliers, and handbills is arranged in three subseries: XI.A. ACT UP, 1988-1992, n.d.; XI.B. Other organizations, 1991-1992, n.d.; and XI.C. Miscellaneous material, 1989, 1993, n.d. See Series XV. Addenda for additional materials.
  - XI.A. ACT UP, 1988, circa 1990, 1992, n.d., 557766; 4 boxes
    Subseries XI.A. ACT UP is arranged alphabetically by subject and includes materials relating to the following actions, organizations, and issues: Target Bush, Center for Disease Control (CDC), Confidentiality, Gay Pride Day, Health Issues (general), Latino Issues, and St. Patrick's Cathedral.
    - Abbott Lab action, n.d.; 557767 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Abortion right demonstration, Washington, DC, 557768 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 2)
    - ACT UP Plan an Action, n.d.; 557769 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 11)
    - AIDS, 557770
      - Action, Baltimore, Maryland, 557771 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 3)
      - AIDS Advisory Council demonstration, New York, n.d.; 557772 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 4)
      - AIDS Cure Project, n.d.; 557773; Formerly known as the Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS. (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 7)
      - AIDS Institute conference, n.d.; 557774 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 8)
      - AIDS Institute conference demonstration, n.d.; 557775 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 6)
      - Czar, n.d.; 557776 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 5)
      - Memorial, Greenwich Village, New York City, n.d.; 557777 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 9)
      - Prevention walk, n.d.; 557778 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 10)
    - Ailes, Roger, n.d.; 557779; Media director to Rudy Giuliani (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 12)
    - American Medical Association (AMA) conference zap, n.d.; 557780 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 14)
    - Angels in America, n.d.; 557781 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 15)
    - Anti-war, n.d.; 557782 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 16)
    - Astra Pharmaceuticals demonstration, n.d.; 557783 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 17)
    - ATR [AIDS Treatment Registry?], Inc. benefit, n.d.; 557784 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 13)
    - Barbara McClintock Project to Cure AIDS, n.d.; 557785; Later known as the AIDS Cure Project. For more information, see Series VIII. Subjects. (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 18)
    - Benetton's demonstration: Beware, n.d.; 557786 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 19)
    - Blue Cross and Blue Shield, 557787 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 20)
    - Board of Education, n.d.; 557788 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 21)
    - Broadway Cares phone zap, n.d.; 557789 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 22)
    - Buckley, Mr. and Mrs. William F., 557790 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 23)
    - Burroughs Wellcome zap, n.d.; 557791 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 24)
    - Bush, George: Target Bush, n.d.; 557792 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 25-28)
    - Califano, Joseph: Demonstration, n.d.; 557793 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 29)
    - Call-in, n.d.; 557794 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 30)
    - Campaign, 1992; 557795 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 31)
    - Canadian immigration, n.d.; 557796 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 32)
    - Centers for Disease Control, n.d.; 557797 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 33)
    - Chapters, 557798
      - California, 557799
        - Los Angeles, n.d.; 557800 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 18)
        - San Francisco, n.d.; 557801 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 20)
      - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 557802 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 19)
    - Children with AIDS/HIV, n.d.; 557803 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 34)
    - Circlek Corporation, n.d.; 557804 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 35)
    - City Hall, n.d.; 557805 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 36)
    - Clinton, n.d.; 557806 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 37)
    - Committees, 557807
      - Alternative and Holistic, 557808 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 6)
      - Caucus of Asian and Pacific Islanders, 557809 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 7)
      - City Issues working group, n.d.; 557810 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 8)
      - Congressional Action working group, n.d.; 557811 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 9)
      - Latino/a, n.d.; 557812 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 10)
      - Lesbian AIDS Action fact sheet, n.d.; 557813 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 11)
      - Majority Actions committee, n.d.; 557814 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 12)
      - Media committee, n.d.; 557815 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 13)
      - Pediatric committee, n.d.; 557816 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 14)
      - TB working group, n.d.; 557817 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 15)
      - Youth Brigade, n.d.; 557818 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 16)
      - Youth Education Life Line (YELL), 557819 (Reel 154, Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Confidentiality, n.d.; 557820 (Reel 152, Box 192, Folder 38)
    - Cosmopolitan magazine, n.d.; 557821 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Countdown 18 Month Plan, n.d.; 557822 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Cuomo, Mario, n.d.; 557823 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 3)
    - Daiichi Pharmaceutical: Target, n.d.; 557824 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 6)
    - D'Amato, Al, n.d.; 557825 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Democratic and Republican parties demonstration, 557826 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 4)
    - Dinkins, David, n.d.; 557827 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 7)
    - DIVA TV, n.d.; 557828 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Division of AIDS Services, n.d.; 557829 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Division of AIDS Services zap, n.d.; 557830 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Don't Be Silent, n.d.; 557831 (Reel 152, Box 193, Folder 11)